Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963 - 1994 UA.03.61.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1963-1994, bulk 1985-1993
  - Subject Files, 1963-1993 and undated, bulk 1985-1993. Accessions UA95-58, UA95-80, UA95-113, UA95-114, UA96-30, UA96-77, and UA97-65.
    - Political Correctness, 1991 Jan. 1-1992 May 31 (Box 71)
    - Political Science Department, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Political Science Department, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Political Science Department, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Presidential Awards, 1989 (Box 71)
    - Presidential Awards, 1988 (Box 71)
    - Presidential Awards, 1987 (Box 71)
    - Presidential Awards, 1984-1986 (Box 71)
    - Primate Center, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 71)
    - Private Adjudication Center, 1987-1991 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Psychical Research Foundation, undated (Box 72)
    - Psychology Department, 1991 July 1 (Box 72)
    - Psychology Department, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Psychology Department, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Public Safety, 1985 June-1989 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Pye, Kenneth A., 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Rankings, 1991 July 1 (Box 72)
    - Rankings of Colleges & Universities, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Real Estate, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Referral Logs, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Referral Logs, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 72)
    - Referral Logs, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Referral Logs, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Registrar, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Registrar: Cahow, Clark, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Religion Department, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Research Support: Office, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Research Support: Duke University, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Retirement Community, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Retirement Community, 1983 Sept.-1987 June 30 (Box 73)
    - Retreat, President's, undated (Box 73)
    - RJR Nabisco, 1986 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 73)
    - RJR Nabisco, 1986 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Romance Languages, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Safety, 1989 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Sanford, Terry, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Scarritt College, 1986 Dec.-1987 Jan. (Box 74)
    - Science Resource Initiative (SRI), 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Science Resource Initiative, 1990 Apr. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Science Resource Initiative (# 2), 1990 Jan. 1-1990 Mar. 31 (Box 74)
    - Science Resource Initiative, 1989 July 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 74)
    - Science Resource Initiative, 1988 May-1989 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Service Master, 1989 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 74)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration, undated (Box 74)
    - Sexual Harassment, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Skarulis, Patricia: Vice Chancellor for Information Systems, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Skarulis, Patricia, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Sociology Department, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1987-1991 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Southeastern Universities Research Association, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Southern Regional Education Board, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Space Planning, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Space Planning, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Special Events, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Stanford University, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Starr Foundation, 1983-1991 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Statistics and Decision Sciences, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Steam Plant, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 75)
    - Speeches, 1985-1993 and undated. (Box 76)
      This subseries of the Subject Files series consists of drafts and final version of speeches and presentations given by Dr. Brodie during his tenure as President. Related files in boxes 3-16 contain source materials and other working files for many of these speches.
      Speeches are arranged, for the most part, in chronological order.
      - Miscellaneous Published Speeches, undated (2 folders) (Box 76)
      - Transparencies and Graphs: Various, undated (Box 76)
      - High Point Rotary Club Speech, 1985 Jan. 31 (Box 76)
      - Speech to Freshman, 1985 Aug. 31 (Box 76)
      - Quarter Century Banquet, 1985 Sept. 13 (Box 76)
      - Inaugural Address to Faculty, 1985 Sept. 26 (Box 76)
      - Inaugural Address, 1985 Sept. 28 (Box 76)
      - Chicago Address, 1985 Oct. 9 (Box 76)
      - Alumni Reception Remarks: Chicago, 1985 Oct. 9 (Box 76)
      - Alumni Reception Remarks: Charlotte, 1985 Oct. 11 (Box 76)
      - Gerontology Building Dedication Remarks, 1985 Oct. 12 (Box 76)
      - B. N. Duke Leadership Fund, 1985 Oct. 15 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Seniors, 1985 Oct. 28 (Box 76)
      - Class of 1986, 1985 Oct. 28 (Box 76)
      - Duke Seminar, 1985 Nov. 2 (Box 76)
      - Watauga Club, 1985 Nov. 5 (Box 76)
      - Policy Sciences Luncheon, 1985 Nov. 8 (Box 76)
      - Dean's Council, Engineering Speech, 1985 Nov. 15 (Box 76)
      - Tree Lighting, 1985 Dec. 2 (Box 76)
      - Duke Endowment Dinner, 1985 Dec. 2 (Box 76)
      - Address to Board of Trustees, 1985 Dec. 6 (Box 76)
      - Duke/Durham Luncheon Address, 1985 Dec. 8 (Box 76)
      - January Freshman Speech, 1986 Jan. 3 (Box 76)
      - Luncheon Remarks, College of Bishops, 1986 Jan. 9 (Box 76)
      - Martin Luther King Birthday, 1986 Jan. 15 (Box 76)
      - Duke Seminar, 1986 Jan. 24 (Box 76)
      - Faculty & Staff Solicitation, 1986 Jan. 30 (Box 76)
      - North Carolina Press Awards Presentation, 1986 Jan. 31 (Box 76)
      - Job Enhancement Program, 1985 Sept. 16-1986 Nov. 3 (Box 76)
      - Martin Luther King Speech, 1986 Jan. 20 (Box 76)
      - Durham Academy, 1986 Jan. 23 (Box 76)
      - A Psychiatrist Looks at Apartheid, 1986 Feb. 3 (Box 76)
      - Bryan Research Center Dedication, 1986 Feb. 12 (Box 76)
      - Cities Chairmen, 1986 Feb. 21 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Council on Women's Studies, 1986 Feb. 27 (Box 76)
      - Trustees Dinner, 1986 Feb. 28 (Box 76)
      - Pan-Hellenic and Intra-Fraternity Council, 1986 Mar. 11 (Box 76)
      - Speech Address to Black Applicants, 1986 Mar. 13 (Box 76)
      - Speech Divinity Board of Visitors, 1986 Mar. 14 (Box 76)
      - Speech ASDU Legislature, 1986 Mar. 24 (Box 76)
      - Speech NY, 1986 Apr. 2 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1986 Apr. 14 (Box 76)
      - State of the University Board of Trustees Address, 1986 May 2 (Box 76)
      - Atlanta Alumni Dinner, 1986 May 31 (Box 76)
      - Speech Lake Junaluska Methodists, 1986 June 6 (Box 76)
      - Address to the North Carolina Conference of United Methodist Church, 1986 June 2 (Box 76)
      - Public Safety Address, 1986 June 11 (Box 76)
      - David Thomas Dinner, 1986 June 13 (Box 76)
      - Address to Class of 1990, undated (Box 76)
      - Academic Council, 1986 June 18 (Box 76)
      - Board of Trustees, 1986 Sept. 26 (Box 76)
      - Centurion Dinner, 1986 Sept. 26 (Box 76)
      - Luncheon Hudson Family, 1986 Sept. 27 (Box 76)
      - Reunion Gift Presentation (Duke UVA game), 1986 Sept. 27 (Box 76)
      - Presidential Awards, Quarter Century Banquet, 1986 Sept. 30 (Box 76)
      - Fuqua Symposium on US Business & South Africa, 1986 Oct. 2 (Box 76)
      - Address to Class of 1987, 1986 Oct. 8 (Box 76)
      - Secondary School Counselor Conference, 1986 Oct. 9 (Box 76)
      - Introduction of Robert S. McNamara, 1986 Oct. 15 (Box 76)
      - Inauguration of C. D. Spangler Jr., 1986 Oct. 17 (Box 76)
      - Neil Williams Homecoming Speech, 1986 Oct. 24 (Box 76)
      - Madrid Speech, 1986 Oct. 23 (Box 76)
      - Remarks to the Class of 1946 (Hudson, Simpson, Stern, Westen), 1986 Nov. 7 (Box 76)
      - Speech: Philadelphia, 1986 Nov. 12 (Box 76)
      - Introduction of Peter Williams, 1986 Nov. 20 (Box 76)
      - Christmas Tree Lighting, 1986 Dec. 9 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Faculty, 1986 Dec. 11 (Box 76)
      - Founders Day Convocation, 1986 Dec. 11 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Board of Trustees, 1986 Dec. 12 (Box 76)
      - Founders Society Dinner, 1986 Dec. 13 (Box 76)
      - Founders Day Chapel Service, 1986 Dec. 14 (Box 76)
      - Soccer Team Welcome, 1986 Dec. 15 (Box 76)
      - Martin Luther King Memorial Speech, 1987 Jan. 19 (Box 76)
      - Hough Introduction, 1987 Jan. 21 (Box 76)
      - Miami Alumni Group, 1987 Jan. 27 (Box 76)
      - Duke Seminar Speech, 1987 Feb. 20 (Box 76)
      - Raleigh Alumni Meeting: Blue Devil Present, 1987 Mar. 17 (Box 76)
      - Address to Librarians, 1987 Mar. 19 (Box 76)
      - Black Students Speech, 1987 Mar. 19 (Box 76)
      - Baltimore Address, 1987 Apr. 6 (Box 76)
      - ROTC Address, 1987 Apr. 10 (Box 76)
      - Comprehensive Cancer Center Welcome, 1987 Apr. 15 (Box 76)
      - Address to Senior Athletes, Renne Award, 1987 Apr. 21 (Box 76)
      - New Admissions, 1987 Apr. 21 (Box 76)
      - Board of Trustees Address, 1987 May 8 (Box 76)
      - Trustee Dinner (Awards to John Koskinen & Kay Miller), 1987 May 8 (Box 76)
      - Thomas Luncheon & Groundbreaking, 1987 May 9 (Box 76)
      - Dinner Honorary Degree & Alumni Award, 1987 May 9 (Box 76)
      - Acceptance of Gift from Class of 1937, 1987 May 9 (Box 76)
      - University of Richmond, 1987 May 10 (Box 76)
      - Talent Identification Program Welcome, 1987 May 15 (Box 76)
      - Land Resource Committee Address, 1987 May 21 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Class of 1991, 1987 Aug. 26 (Box 76)
      - 1987 Graduate & Professional Convocation, 1987 Aug. 28 (Box 76)
      - Parents Committee Dinner, 1987 Sept. 18 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Board of Trustees, 1987 Sept. 25 (Box 76)
      - Trustee Dinner: Barringer and Pye, 1987 Sept. 25 (Box 76)
      - Richmond Address, 1987 Oct. 1 (Box 76)
      - Opening of the Center for Biochemical Engineering, 1987 Oct. 2 (Box 76)
      - Address to the Senior Class, 1987 Oct. 7 (Box 76)
      - Quarter Century Banquet, 1987 Oct. 12 (Box 76)
      - RJR Nabisco: Fuqua Press Conference, 1987 Oct. 21 (Box 76)
      - Washington Duke Club: Few Association, 1987 Oct. 31 (Box 76)
      - Trent Foundation Dinner, 1987 Nov. 12 (Box 76)
      - Christmas Tree Lighting Ceremony, 1987 Dec. 1 (Box 76)
      - Faculty Address, 1987 Dec. 10 (Box 76)
      - Founders Day Convocation, 1987 Dec. 10 (Box 76)
      - Centurion Dinner, 1987 Dec. 11 (Box 76)
      - Founders Society Dinner, 1987 Dec. 12 (Box 76)
      - Reagan Visit: Substance Abuse Conference, 1988 Feb. 8 (Box 76)
      - Dorm Groundbreaking, 1988 Mar. 2 (Box 76)
      - Los Angeles Alumni Address, 1988 Mar. 7 (Box 76)
      - Address to Black Applicants, 1988 Mar. 17 (Box 76)
      - Durham Rotary Club, 1988 Mar. 21 (Box 76)
      - Introduction of Derek Bok (Terry Sanford Distinguished Lecturer), 1988 Mar. 23 (Box 76)
      - Engineering Dean's Council, undated (Box 76)
      - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1988 Apr. 11 (Box 76)
      - Washington DC Alumni Reception, 1988 Apr. 18 (Box 76)
      - Triangle Area Research Directors Club, 1988 Apr. 19 (Box 76)
      - Address to Board of Trustees, 1988 May 6 (Box 76)
      - Baccalaureate Services, 1988 May 6-1988 May 7 (Box 76)
      - Trustee Dinner, 1988 May 6 (Box 76)
      - Acceptance of Gift from Class of 1938, 1988 May 7 (Box 76)
      - Dinner Honorary Degree & Alumni Award, 1988 May 6 (Box 76)
      - Commencement, 1988 May 8 (Box 76)
      - Boston Alumni Dinner, 1988 May 18 (Box 76)
      - Wilmington, Delaware Alumni Reception, 1988 May 25 (Box 76)
      - Proclamation for Duke Employees, 1988 June 6 (Box 76)
      - AMA Conference on Adolescent Health, 1988 June 9 (Box 76)
      - Marine Lab Fiftieth Anniversary, 1988 June 11 (Box 76)
      - Neil Williams Celebration, 1988 June 14 (Box 77)
      - Winston-Salem Alumni Event, 1988 June 16 (Box 77)
      - American Orthopedic Association, 1988 June 21 (Box 77)
      - Eye Center Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1988 June 22 (Box 77)
      - Address to the Freshman Class 1992, 1988 Apr. 24 (Box 77)
      - Opening Convocation, 1988 Apr. 24 (Box 77)
      - Presentation of Jesse Jackson, 1988 Aug. 28 (Box 77)
      - AT&T Gift Announcement, 1988 Sept. 13 (Box 77)
      - Duke/UNC Conference on Education, 1988 Sept. 16 (Box 77)
      - St. Phillips Adult Education Class, 1988 Sept. 18 (Box 77)
      - Tribute to Dr. Anlyan, 1988 Sept. 23 (Box 77)
      - Centurion Dinner, 1988 Sept. 24 (Box 77)
      - Alumni Reunion Remarks, 1988 Sept. 24 (Box 77)
      - J. Walter Thompson Archives Reception, 1988 Sept. 26 (Box 77)
      - Carnegie Task Force on Families and Adolescents, DC, 1988 Sept. 29-1988 Sept. 30 (Box 77)
      - Tribute to Sam Katz, 1988 Sept. 30 (Box 77)
      - Address to the Senior Class of 1988, 1988 Oct. 5 (Box 77)
      - Quarter Century Banquet, 1988 Oct. 13 (Box 77)
      - Alumni Reunion Class, 1988 Oct. 22 (Box 77)
      - Parents Comm. & Reunion Group, 1988 Nov. 5 (Box 77)
      - Cancer Center Luncheon, 1988 Nov. 7 (Box 77)
      - United Negro College Fund, 1988 Nov. 9 (Box 77)
      - American Tobacco Press Conference, 1988 Nov. 17 (Box 77)
      - Tree Lighting Ceremony, 1988 Nov. 29 (Box 77)
      - Founder's Convocation, 1988 Dec. 8 (Box 77)
      - Address to Faculty, 1988 Dec. 8 (Box 77)
      - Founders Dinner, 1988 Dec. 10 (Box 77)
      - Winston-Salem Rotary Club Speech, 1989 Jan. 10 (Box 77)
      - The Campaign for Duke, 1989 Jan. 23 (Box 77)
      - General Alumni Association, 1989 Jan. 28 (Box 77)
      - Girls & Women in Sports, 1989 Feb. 4 (Box 77)
      - Rhoads Retirement Speech, 1989 Feb. 11 (Box 77)
      - Poverty in South Africa, 1989 Feb. 16 (Box 77)
      - Women's Studies 150th Symposium, 1989 Mar. 3 (Box 77)
      - Address to Black Applicants. 1989 Mar. 23 (Box 77)
      - CIDR Dinner & Sanford Introduction, 1989 Apr. 7 (Box 77)
      - Confronting Rape Culture Colloquium, 1989 Apr. 8 (Box 77)
      - Half Century Club, 1989 Apr. 8 (Box 77)
      - KROC Award, 1989 Apr. 10 (Box 77)
      - Black Academic Surgeons & Sullivan, 1989 Apr. 13 (Box 77)
      - J. B. Fuqua Bust Unveiling, 1989 Apr. 14 (Box 77)
      - Duke Gardens Fiftieth Birthday, 1989 Apr. 15 (Box 77)
      - Senior Athletes Banquet, 1989 Apr. 18 (Box 77)
      - Julian Abele Banquet, 1989 Apr. 21 (Box 77)
      - Pinehurst Alumni Reception, 1989 Apr. 26 (Box 77)
      - Black Ministries. 1989 May 1 (Box 77)
      - Commencement & Graduation Weekend, 1989 May 12-1989 May 14 (Box 77)
      - St. Louis Alumni Reception, 1989 May 23 (Box 77)
      - Detroit Alumni Luncheon, 1989 June 7 (Box 77)
      - Project Build Remarks, 1989 Aug. 18 (Box 77)
      - Resident Advisors & Freshman AC's, 1989 Aug. 23 (Box 77)
      - Convocation & Freshman Address, 1989 Aug. 24 (Box 77)
      - Address to Alumni Clubs Leadership, 1989 Sept. 8 (Box 77)
      - Academic Council Remarks, 1989 Sept. 21 (Box 77)
      - Duke Family Reunion Tea, 1989 Sept. 30 (Box 77)
      - Quarter Century Banquets, 1989 Oct. 5 (Box 77)
      - Address to Alumni Reunion Groups, 1989 Oct. 7 (Box 77)
      - Senior Address, 1989 Oct. 10 (Box 77)
      - National Humanities Center, 1989 Oct. 20 (Box 77)
      - International Studies Board of Visitors, 1989 Oct. 27 (Box 77)
      - R. David Thomas Center Dedication, 1989 Oct. 27 (Box 77)
      - Address to Reunion Group, 1989 Oct. 28 (Box 77)
      - Address to President's Council, 1989 Nov. 10 (Box 77)
      - State of University Address to Reunion Classes, 1989 Nov. 11 (Box 77)
      - Trinity Board of Visitors, 1989 Nov. 17 (Box 77)
      - Faculty Address, 1989 Dec. 7 (Box 77)
      - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, 1990 Jan. 15 (Box 77)
      - Center for Documentary Studies, 1990 Jan. 23 (Box 77)
      - Problems of Knowledge Seminar, 1990 Jan. 24 (Box 77)
      - D. Allan Bromley, 1990 Jan. 25 (Box 77)
      - Address to the Theta Chi Fraternity, 1990 Feb. 8 (Box 77)
      - Paul B. Williams Media Center Dedication, 1990 Feb. 21 (Box 77)
      - Bryan Neurology Center Dedication, 1990 Feb. 22 (Box 77)
      - C. Eric Lincoln: Howard Johnson Award, 1990 Feb. 23 (Box 77)
      - Campaign for Duke Executive Committee, 1990 Feb. 24 (Box 77)
      - Speech to Graduate and Professional Students Council, 1990 Mar. 19 (Box 77)
      - Dave Stedman Citation (NCCBI), 1990 Mar. 21 (Box 77)
      - Development Lunch and Pres. Council Reception in New York, 1990 Apr. 4 (Box 77)
      - Management Club, 1990 Apr. 17 (Box 77)
      - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1990 Apr. 24 (Box 77)
      - Baccalaureate Service, 1990 May 11 (Box 77)
      - Trustee Dinner, 1990 May 11 (Box 77)
      - Commencement, 1990 May 13 (Box 77)
      - Herbert Pardes Introduction, 1990 May 13 (Box 77)
      - Admissions Talk, 1990 May (Box 77)
      - Durham Academy Commencement Speech, 1990 June 2 (Box 77)
      - San Francisco, 1990 June 10-1990 June 13 (Box 77)
      - Headmasters Address, 1990 June 21 (Box 77)
      - Project Build, 1990 Aug. 20 (Box 77)
      - Address to RAs/FACs, 1990 Aug. 22 (Box 77)
      - Convocation and Freshman Address, 1990 Aug. 23 (Box 77)
      - Charles Johnson Celebration, 1990 Sept. 14 (Box 77)
      - Remarks to Alumni Reunion Class, 1990 Sept. 22 (Box 77)
      - Lord Foundation Awards and Dinner, 1990 Sept. 25 (Box 77)
      - Duke Endowment Dinner, 1990 Oct. 1 (Box 77)
      - Remarks at J. Walter Thompson Reception, 1990 Oct. 3 (Box 77)
      - Speech to Reunion Group and Parents Committee, 1990 Oct. 20 (Box 77)
      - Address to the Senior Class-Class of 1991, 1990 Oct. 30 (Box 77)
      - International Speech Given at President's Council Luncheon, 1990 Nov. 2 (Box 77)
      - Address to NC Bar Foundation, 1990 Nov. 9 (Box 77)
      - Speech to Greensboro Alumni, 1990 Nov. 9 (Box 78)
      - Lilly Family Gift Reception, 1990 Nov. 17 (Box 78)
      - Address to the Faculty, 1990 Dec. 6 (Box 78)
      - Founders' Convocation, 1990 Dec. 6 (Box 78)
      - Martin Luther King Celebration, 1991 Jan. 21 (Box 78)
      - NAS/IOM Regional Roundtable, 1991 Jan. 28 (Box 78)
      - Introduction of Dan Blue, 1991 Mar. 7 (Box 78)
      - Black Student Alliance Invitational, 1991 Mar. 21 (Box 78)
      - Educating for Science Forum, 1991 Mar. 26 (Box 78)
      - Women's Studies Symposium, 1991 Apr. 5 (Box 78)
      - Terry Sanford Distinguished Lecture, 1991 Apr. 11 (Box 78)
      - Speech to ROTC, 1991 Apr. 20 (Box 78)
      - Commencement, 1991 May 12 (Box 78)
      - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1991 Apr. 24 (Box 78)
      - Remarks to Dallas and New Orleans Group, 1991 June 10-1991 June 11 (Box 78)
      - Project Build Speech File, 1991 Aug. 22 (Box 78)
      - Freshman Address, 1991 Aug. 29 (Box 78)
      - Alumni Leadership, 1991 Aug. 13 (Box 78)
      - Alumni Reunion Groups, 1991 Aug. 21 (Box 78)
      - Trustee Dinner, 1991 Aug. 27 (Box 78)
      - Remarks to Duke Endowment Board, 1991 Aug. 30 (Box 78)
      - Duke Endowment Dinner, 1991 Aug. 30 (Box 78)
      - CCB Gold Star Awards Banquet, 1991 Oct. 2 (Box 78)
      - Keynote Address at Gold Star Award Dinner (CCB), 1991 Oct. 2 (Box 78)
      - Alumni Reunion Groups and Annual Fund Parents' Committee, 1991 Oct. 5 (Box 78)
      - President's Council Dinner: Duke and Environment, 1991 Oct. 31 (Box 78)
      - State of University Address to Alumni Groups, 1991 Nov. 2 (Box 78)
      - Watauga Club, 1991 Dec. 3 (Box 78)
      - Founders' Convocation, 1991 Dec. 5 (Box 78)
      - Address to the Faculty, 1992 Jan. 23 (Box 78)
      - Duke Seminar, 1991 Jan. 31 (Box 78)
      - Presidential Awards Luncheon, 1992 Feb. 11 (Box 78)
      - Matthew Sclafani Memorial Service, 1992 Feb. 13 (Box 78)
      - Alumni Development Reception in Miami, 1992 Feb. 21 (Box 78)
      - Retirement of Laettner's Jersey, 1992 Feb. 26 (Box 78)
      - Capital Campaign/Centurions Dinner, 1992 Feb. 28 (Box 78)
      - Introduction of Frank Donatelli: 1492, 1992 Feb. 29 (Box 78)
      - Memorial Service for William Zung, 1992 Apr. 8 (Box 78)
      - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1992 Apr. 27 (Box 78)
      - High Point University Commencement Address, 1992 May 2 (Box 78)
      - APA Annual Meeting, DC, 1992 May 3 (Box 78)
      - Dinner to Honor Ed Pratt/Pfizer, 1992 May 14 (Box 78)
      - Trustee Dinner Honoring Ken Royall, 1992 May 15 (Box 78)
      - Commencement, 1992 May 17 (Box 78)
      - President's Advisors on Science and Technology and Bromley Introduction. 1992 July 21 (Box 78)
      - Address to the Class of 1996, 1992 Aug. 27 (Box 78)
      - Rotary Club Speech, 1992 Sept. 14 (Box 78)
      - Law School Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1992 Sept. 19 (Box 78)
      - SRC Groundbreaking and Trustees Dinner to honor Leon Levine, 1992 Sept. 25 (Box 78)
      - Centennial Celebration of Trinity College, 1992 Sept. 26 (Box 78)
      - Alumni Speech, 1992 Oct. 24 (Box 78)
      - State of the University Presented to Alumni, 1992 Nov. 7 (Box 78)
      - Remarks at Building the Partnership for Change (Royall Conference), 1992 Dec. 10 (Box 78)
      - Founders' Day Convocation, 1992 Dec. 10 (Box 78)
      - Retreat of Durham County Commissioners, 1992 Dec. 17 (Box 78)
      - Martin Luther King Day Celebration, 1993 Jan. 18 (Box 78)
      - Address to the Faculty, 1993 Jan. 21 (Box 78)
      - Reggie Howard Scholarship Recognition, 1993 Apr. 17 (Box 78)
      - ASDU Speech, 1993 Apr. 21 (Box 78)
      - Children's Mental Health: T. Gore, 1993 Apr. 24 (Box 78)
      - Address to the Senior Athletes, 1993 Apr. 26 (Box 78)
      - Introductions of Spicer and White, 1993 Apr. 29 (Box 78)
      - Commencement, 1993 May 16 (Box 78)
      - Public Safety Dinner, 1993 June 10 (Box 78)
    - Stores Operation, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Student Affairs: Janet Dickerson, 1991 May-1992 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Student Affairs: William Griffith, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Student Affairs: William Griffith, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Student Affairs: Griffith, William, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Student Affairs, Committee to Honor W. M. Griffith, undated (Box 79)
    - Student Affairs, Search Committee for VP of Student Affairs, undated (Box 79)
    - Student Housing, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Student Housing, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Student Housing, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Students: Letters from Parents, 1987 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Students: Letters from Parents, 1985 July-1987 June (Box 79)
    - Students: Miscellaneous, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 79)
    - Students: Miscellaneous, 1991 Jan. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 80)
    - Students: Miscellaneous, 1990 May 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 80)
    - Students: Miscellaneous, 1989 July 1-1990 Apr. 30 (Box 80)
    - Students: Miscellaneous, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 80)
    - Students: Miscellaneous, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 80)
    - Students: Orientation, 1985 (Box 80)
    - Students: Race Relations, undated (Box 80)
    - Suggestion Box, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 80)
    - Suggestion Box, 1988 Jan.-1989 June 30 (Box 80)
    - Super Computer, 1986 Dec.-1989 June 30 (Box 80)
    - Super Conductor, 1986 June-1989 Mar. (Box 81)
    - Talent Identification Program (TIP), 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Talent Identification Program, 1987 July-1989 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Talent Identification Program, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Teaching, Masters in, 1986-1991 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Technology Center, 1985 July-1989 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Telecommunications, 1985-1991 June 30 (Box 81)
    - TIAA CREF, 1985 Dec.-1987 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Trinity Board of Visitors, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Trinity Board of Visitors, 1988 Apr.-1989 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Tuition, 1985 July-1987 June 30 (Box 81)
    - Undergraduate Faculty Council of Arts & Sciences, 1987-1991 June 30 (Box 81)